NGUYỄN VIỆT HÙNG

.NFT DFVFI OPFR



**** 0395746139



hnv2311@gmail.com PHo Chi Minh City





23/11/2001



portfolio.hocduthu.com

PROFILE INFO

Dotnet Developer with 1 year of experience developing web and web API applications using .NET Core, MS SQL, and MySQL. Understanding object-oriented programming principles, software development methodologies, git version control, and agile practices. Self-motivated, proactive, and capable of working independently as well as in a team environment, and also ability to analyze and design databases

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2023 - May 2024

P&B Food Viet Nam I Thu Dau Mot City, Binh Duong Province

Freelancer Fulltime

- Lead and manage an IT team collaborating with P&B's internal team to define project requirements and deliverables
- Design the database based on the requirements and build the code base structure for the Backend, using .NET 8 technology
- Implement features related to authentication and authorization, integrate payment through payment gateways PayOs and Momo
- · Build and manage the deployment process using GitHub Action and Docker container
- Develop a Flutter mobile application for P&B's delivery staff

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

FPT Software | District 9, Ho Chi Minh City

.Net Intern

- Analyze existing application code, write unit tests, and debug the application
- Build and deploy the system to Azure cloud

PROJECT

All projects featured on my portfolio

Portfolio link: portfolio.hocduthu.com/project

CERTIFICATE

Software Development Lifecycle

Google Project Management

Linux Fundamentals

Computer Communications

Coursera @

Coursera @

Coursera @

Coursera @

EDUCATION

2019 - 2024 | FPT University **Bachelor of Software Engineering**

SKILLS

Programming languages:

· C#, Java, Dart

Framework:

• .Net, basic Flutter

Database:

SQL (SQL Server), MySQL

Cloud:

• Basic Azure, AWS, VPS

Others:

- · GitHub, Unit Test, Redis
- Linux OS, Docker

ACTIVITIES

• Write and share effective articles on technology and engineering on my blog Học Đủ Thứ